socialphy.com 2012-06-26

# Socialphy - Collective Intelligence

## Privacy Policy

These statements are aimed at informing users about how Socialphy treats personal data so that users may determine whether or not they shall freely and voluntarily provide their personal data when required, or those data they may obtain from the use of any service available in Socialphy.

Socialphy, considers that any kind of information related to one user is of personal nature and, therefore, Socialphy watches out users' information privacy and confidentiality. Users' information confidentiality shall imply keeping safe files and/or data banks or bases in such a way that access by non-authorized third parties is restricted.

For questions about this Policy or any circumstance related to the treatment of personal information, users may write to this email: denuncias@socialphy.com

### 1\. Willingness to provide Data

This Policy is aimed at informing users about how Socialphy treats personal data so that users may determine whether or not they shall freely and voluntarily provide their personal data when required or those data they may obtain from the use of any service available in "http://socialphy.com".

As a general rule, when in order to use a service or to access certain content, personal data is required, providing said data is not obligatory, except when it is specifically stated that said data are required for providing the service or accessing the content.

### 2\. Authorization to use Personal Information

A user providing his/her personal data expressly authorizes Socialphy to use said provided data for the purposes herein mentioned. That also implies acceptance of all terms contained in this Policy and the General Terms and Conditions.

### 3\. Information Collection and Use.

The purpose of gathering and treating personal data is to provide, manage, administer, customize, update and improve the services and contents made available to the users by Socialphy.

### 4\. Non-Assignment of Data

All personal data collected from users shall be exclusively used in-house. Whenever personal data is gathered under a direct relationship with one user, in respect of users' privacy and confidentiality, Socialphy shall not assign nor transfer said personal information to any third party different from Socialphy or its associates.

**Socialphy shall only share users' personal information with third parties in the following events:**

  * When there is a legal duty to do so.
  * When a competent Court Order is issued.

### 5\. Site Notices

Occasionally, data may be used for sending notices to users in relation to products and services provided by Socialphy.

### 6\. Access to Information by the People related to the Registered Data

Thus, users may exercise rights to access, correct, cancel or challenge data, as it shall be herein below stated.

The exercise of said rights may be made by each user by means of a notice addressed to Socialphy, according to the contact information herein provided.

Once users have entered data, Socialphy shall correct, remove or update personal data referring to the user involved, as it may correspond.

The removal of any data shall not be made when it could result in any damage to lawful third parties' rights or interests or when there if a legal duty to preserve those data.

**Right to Require Data Correction:** In principle, the right to require correction may be exercised in case of false, inaccurate, inexact or wrong data. Acknowledging that right implies acknowledging to preserve information truthfulness, a condition that contributes to information quality.

**Right to Require Data Update:** Update means keeping data up to date, that means, that any piece of information matches with the piece of time in which it is provided

**Right to Add and Dissociate:** Users may require the addition of information to their registered data when they consider them incomplete in such a way that said data reflect the piece of reality which they represent.

Likewise, they may also require dissociation of data whose quality and features only allow treatment thereof without establishing any association or relation to a data holder.

**Right to Removal and Confidentiality:** "Removing" any data implies definitely deleting said data from a file or registry; that means full elimination without any trace of a former registration.

### 7\. Appropriate Security Methods

Socialphy adopts all logical and physical security measures required by rules and those which are deemed prudent and adequate in order to protect users trusting Socialphy and to protect the personal information gathered from any non-authorized access, alteration or destruction. Socialphy assesses and improves its security systems whenever it is necessary.

### 8\. Amendments to this Policy

In case of any amendment to this Policy, said amendments shall be published in this section. Socialphy reserves the right to amend this Policy at any time for which users shall refer to it on a regular basis.

### 9\. Account Closing

In case a user decides to close his/her Socialphy account, our Privacy Policy shall be in force with respect to that user. All his/her personal information shall be deleted from Socialphy systems.
